{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Geothermal Heating \u0026 Cooling Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40289/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40289,"taskName":"Geothermal Heating or Cooling System - Service","taskDescription":"Service a Geothermal Heating or Cooling System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Geothermal Heating \u0026 Cooling Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1706,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Geothermal Heat Geothermal Heating Geothermal","textMessagingName":"Svc Geo Therm","rolloverLongDesc":"Uses a heat pump in conjunction with a network of pipes that are either buried or sunk in a pond or lake. Very energy efficient because it takes advantage of the relatively steady underground or underwater temperatures.","rolloverShortDesc":"Draws heat or coolness from ground or body of water.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Service a GeoThermal Heating or Cooling System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Geothermal Heating \u0026 Cooling Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Geothermal Heating or Cooling Service","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Geo Thermal Heating or Cooling System - Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Geo Thermal Heating or Cooling Project","urlName":"Geo-Thermal-Heating-or-Cooling-System-Service","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Geothermal Heating \u0026 Cooling Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Geothermal,Heat,cool,energy,efficient,renewable,Geo-exchange","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":590,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40289/":{"taskOID":40289,"originalTaskOID":40289,"setID":590,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4821,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why does it need servicing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4305,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3503,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leakage","answerDisplayText":"Leakage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3725,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Makes odd noises","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noises","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4969,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pump problem","answerDisplayText":"Pump problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1973,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doesn't get cool enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get cool enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1794,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","answerDisplayText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4819,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of geothermal system do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open loop water source","answerDisplayText":"Open loop water source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3077,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Horizontal closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6679,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vertical closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Vertical closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5803,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slinky closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Slinky closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4775,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pond closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Pond closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10162,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4820,"questionDisplayText":"Heat Distribution System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is the heat distributed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2800,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Geothermal heat pump/duct work","answerDisplayText":"Geothermal heat pump/duct work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3179,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In-floor radiant heat via circulating pipes","answerDisplayText":"In-floor radiant heat via circulating pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":952,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Baseboard radiators","answerDisplayText":"Baseboard radiators","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6942,"questionDisplayText":"Age of Equipment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the equipment?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10164,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10165,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10166,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10167,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10168,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4821,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why does it need servicing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4305,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3503,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leakage","answerDisplayText":"Leakage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3725,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Makes odd noises","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noises","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4969,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pump problem","answerDisplayText":"Pump problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1973,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doesn't get cool enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get cool enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1794,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","answerDisplayText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4305,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3503,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leakage","answerDisplayText":"Leakage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3725,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Makes odd noises","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noises","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4969,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pump problem","answerDisplayText":"Pump problem","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1973,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doesn't get cool enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get cool enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1794,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","answerDisplayText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4819,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of geothermal system do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open loop water source","answerDisplayText":"Open loop water source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3077,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Horizontal closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6679,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vertical closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Vertical closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5803,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slinky closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Slinky closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4775,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pond closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Pond closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10162,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open loop water source","answerDisplayText":"Open loop water source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3077,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Horizontal closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Horizontal closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6679,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vertical closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Vertical closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5803,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slinky closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Slinky closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4775,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pond closed loop","answerDisplayText":"Pond closed loop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10162,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4820,"questionDisplayText":"Heat Distribution System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is the heat distributed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2800,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Geothermal heat pump/duct work","answerDisplayText":"Geothermal heat pump/duct work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3179,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In-floor radiant heat via circulating pipes","answerDisplayText":"In-floor radiant heat via circulating pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":952,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Baseboard radiators","answerDisplayText":"Baseboard radiators","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2800,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Geothermal heat pump/duct work","answerDisplayText":"Geothermal heat pump/duct work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3179,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In-floor radiant heat via circulating pipes","answerDisplayText":"In-floor radiant heat via circulating pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":952,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Baseboard radiators","answerDisplayText":"Baseboard radiators","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6942,"questionDisplayText":"Age of Equipment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the equipment?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10164,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10165,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10166,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10167,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10168,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10164,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10165,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10166,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10167,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10168,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}